The serpent who teased
My goddess and my shield, Scorpio's empire rising.
My destiny re-
I found like there's a way to do like VR
And for you to like see what I'm seeing on it that'd be cool to do some day
This is fun like it's like well I have to play more games on it, but
They've been like seeing like
Watching great movies up close like you should if you watch YouTube up close to if you
You see it anybody talking
Hola, oh, that's me
Saying hello to myself. Do you guys hear me? Oh
I slept so much
Hello, oh
That's me again
well
It's the ones gonna talk
They wanted blocked or something now that if you're blocked, I wouldn't see your number
When you're more music
I know it's hard when there's one person in the room
and you'd feel like really like,
ah, my God, zero down.
I don't worry.
Don't even have to be saying anything, don't worry.
Someone will be here in a second
and put up the panel rules.
And thinking about doing some kind of like,
especially like one monthly reading for members,
like what, and they can ask for it anytime.
Okay, native and it's gonna be like a longer reading so me members. I'm just thinking I haven't advertised it enough
That's one of the benefits
I'm psyching in a speedo stars and stripes flash flash turning into tacos with a side of whiplash fish guts on the my
on the table like conspiracies don't die.
Be the sip and wine, cryin' bout her ex, top's gone flyin',
it's a certified mess, she's spillin' all the tea,
now the chat's on fire, Doc's by a cat and her fart's gone viral.
Welcome to the panel, ain't no rules to this,
if you're sayin' turn back, you will not be missed.
Sims in the DMs, chaos in the chat,
this show's more crack than a tick to-
But I guess
Yeah, I found like a weird website look at it. Well, it just basically
Saw someone reacted to it, so I will
You can take this down. Hold on a second
Like in my
In my bike link, too
Yeah, that's what some people that come for and like some people have just been coming and going and sick with the
And say anything are there hey watchers
Here we go
What up?
If you want to look at this website, it's like really strange here
But I think it's probably one of these, you know, it's supposed to be supposed to be weird
You find a few more like real things that well, maybe not compare it but now what it is
Okay, I don't know what this is called big disturbing or something
This is the ho ho ho you see it
I'm gonna need to make it better
Better
And move myself around how do I get around
Okay, can't even see, it's not looking at the website, I can't see it.
Share screen. Oh, here I think I found it.
Okay, do you see it now? Okay, now it's like impossible to read. I'm making a bigger hole.
Is it dedicated to the highest possible quality product?
Our standards of excellence always involve our vision
to grow our product going forward.
Ensure the corporate vision is always our top priority.
Make this bigger or something.
Can you everyone see?
Hi.
Yeah, isn't that sad, Stu?
Sus, who is that?
No, isn't that strange? I lost my following. Oh my gosh in just one day. It'd be terrible everyone
I actually had a live last night. It was not too bad. I had like 20 people in it
I wasn't even doing anything. Maybe I don't know people get bored
Or they could do different things. I don't know maybe they're not up at five in the morning like I am. Okay. Oh my god
Look, it's really weird website though
Can I go? I don't think they'll do anything. Hold on. Let's go like this
corporate home like okay that works I lost my following up to find them like
let them know what is this thing okay there's like all in like German or
that's something else everything's in English it looks like I don't feel like
reading out loud I mean for myself here I bet you can read out loud
Read a ladder? Is there something you can use to read a ladder?
Okay, actually have one on
Thank you very much.
Okay, I mean, what does that mean? Oh
Don't know doesn't mean anything
Hmm. They're like different thing. Okay, it only goes to there while making out of the products. How do they sell?
Okay
How to overcome insomnia sleep deeply how about that one? Oh my god
My love to watch the video, I don't know
Thought myths this looks very like
dark. There's what's going on here.
Vibhela, Petunia. I don't know. It's just I think it was Illuminati maybe. Okay, Nuke us.
Didn't mean to get this.
Where are we?
Does that game work, Slick?
Oh, Los Angeles.
Ah!
I mean, this all does is this.
Oh, oh, look, there's toast.
What is this?
It's the wrong one.
What do you think guys?
Weird.
The weird website.
Hi.
I was like, I have a member.
It's me.
Time is it I was gonna go do IRL but it's like now that everyone's on here. I'm gonna maybe order me some food
And I'll go on my own
Well in this horse this bed stream
I'll be in a better mood when I get back
Right
No one said anything.
Oh, oh yeah, that was like all I said.
That was like, oh my gosh, Sue, Sue, Sue offy said something.
I was like, someone there says this fuck.
I think they're a priestess.
I just heard a bird.
I heard like one of those, what was that?
That was such a weird sound.
Maybe it's on that page though.
If you leave it long enough, it makes noises.
Oh, oh my gosh, this one.
King's Attempts to Pin.
I don't want to read this website anymore.
It's gross.
OK, wow.
OK, I'm just going to end.
I'm sorry, this was not a good idea.
I've been missing in my sleep
Like